export const GeneralKnowledgeQuestions = [
    {
        prompt: "Who was the first Western explorer to reach China?",
        optionA: "Sir Francis Drake",
        optionB: "Marco Polo",
        optionC: "Frederick Cook",
        optionD: "Christopher Columbus",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is the world's longest river?",
        optionA: "Danube",
        optionB: "Amazon",
        optionC: "Mississippi",
        optionD: "Nile",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "How many major planets are there in our solar system?",
        optionA: "8",
        optionB: "7",
        optionC: "9",
        optionD: "10",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What are baby goats called?",
        optionA: "Lamb",
        optionB: "Puppy",
        optionC: "Kid",
        optionD: "Kitten",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is the official animal of the state of California?",
        optionA: "Dog",
        optionB: "Bear",
        optionC: "Cat",
        optionD: "Eagle",
        answer: "B",
    },
]

export const GeographyQuestions = [
    {
        prompt: "Patagonia is part of what two countries?",
        optionA: "Chile and Argentina",
        optionB: "Brazil and Argentina",
        optionC: "Chile and Peru",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which country is known as the Hexagon?",
        optionA: "France",
        optionB: "Spain",
        optionC: "Germany",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Sofia is the capital of what country?",
        optionA: "Belgium",
        optionB: "Bulgaria",
        optionC: "Belarus",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What country refers to themselves as ‘Kiwis’?",
        optionA: "Australia",
        optionB: "South Africa",
        optionC: "New Zealand",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Where would you find Loch Ness?",
        optionA: "Ireland",
        optionB: "Scotland",
        optionC: "Wales",
        answer: "B",
    },
]

export const FoodAndDrinkQuestions = [
    {
        prompt: "What is sushi usually wrapped in?",
        optionA: "Rice noodles",
        optionB: "Pickled ginger",
        optionC: "Edible Seaweed",
        answer: "C"
    },
    {
        prompt: "If you saw Lafite-Rothschild on the menu, what would it be?",
        optionA: "Cheese",
        optionB: "Wine",
        optionC: "Chocolate trifle",
        answer: "B"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Pink Lady, Wisley Crab, Foxwhelps and Lane's Prince Albert are all varities of...?",
        optionA: "Figues",
        optionB: "Pears",
        optionC: "Apples",
        answer: "C"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is allspice also known as?",
        optionA: "Pimento",
        optionB: "Pepper",
        optionC: "All around seasoning",
        answer: "A"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What colour is real Absynthe?",
        optionA: "Clear",
        optionB: "Green",
        optionC: "Black",
        answer: "B"
    },
]